const questions = {"0": [{"question": "How do you say \"Hello.\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "안녕하세요. [An-nyeong-ha-se-yo.]", "valid": true}, {"text": "만나서 반가워요. [Man-na-seo ban-ga-weo-yo.]", "valid": false}, {"text": "안녕히 가세요. [An-nyeong-hi ka-se-yo.]", "valid": false}, {"text": "감사합니다. [Kam-sa-ham-ni-da.]", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"Nice to meet you.\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "만나서 반가워요. [Man-na-seo ban-ga-weo-yo.]", "valid": true}, {"text": "안녕히 계세요. [An-nyeong-hi gye-se-yo.]", "valid": false}, {"text": "감사합니다. [Kam-sa-ham-ni-da.]", "valid": false}, {"text": "천만해요. [Cheon-man-hae-yo.]", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"I am a teacher.\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "저는 선생님이에요. [Jeo-neun seon-saeng-nim-i-e-yo.]", "valid": true}, {"text": "저는 학생이에요. [Jeo-neun hak-saeng-i-e-yo.]", "valid": false}, {"text": "저는 선생님예요. [Jeo-neun seon-saeng-nim-ye-yo.]", "valid": false}, {"text": "저는 가수예요. [Jeo-neun ga-su-ye-yo.]", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"How much is it?\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "얼마예요? [Eol-ma-ye-yo?]", "valid": true}, {"text": "어디에 있어요? [Eo-di-e iss-eo-yo?]", "valid": false}, {"text": "아니에요? [A-ni-e-yo?]", "valid": false}, {"text": "이거예요? [I-geo-ye-yo?]", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"Where are you going now?\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "지금 어디에 가요? [Ji-geum eo-di-e ka-yo?]", "valid": true}, {"text": "지금 어디에 자요? [Ji-geum eo-di-e ja-yo?]", "valid": false}, {"text": "지금 어디에 살아요? [Ji-geum eo-di-e sar-a-yo?]", "valid": false}, {"text": "지금 어디에 있어요? [Ji-geum eo-di-e iss-eo-yo?]", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"Kimchi is delicious.\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "김치가 맛있어요.", "valid": true}, {"text": "김치이 맛있어요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "김치가 안 맛있어요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "김치이 안 맛있어요.", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"It is 3:37p.m.\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "오후 세 시 삼십칠 분이에요.", "valid": true}, {"text": "오후 세 시 사십오 분이에요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "오전 세 시 이십구 분이에요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "오전 세 시 오십삼 분이에요.", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"It is Friday.\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "금요일이에요.", "valid": true}, {"text": "목요일이에요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "화요일이에요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "일요일이에요.", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"Where shall we meet?\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "어디에서 만날까요?", "valid": true}, {"text": "언제 만날까요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "어떻게 만날까요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "누가 만날까요?", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "Choose the correct answer.", "answers": [{"text": "안에 = Inside", "valid": true}, {"text": "위에 = Under", "valid": false}, {"text": "뒤에 = Above", "valid": false}, {"text": "왼쪽 = Right sides", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "Choose the correct answer.", "answers": [{"text": "이다 = To be", "valid": true}, {"text": "이다 = To have", "valid": false}, {"text": "있다 = To be", "valid": false}, {"text": "이따 = To have", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "Choose the correct answer.", "answers": [{"text": "나무 = Tree", "valid": true}, {"text": "너무 = Tree", "valid": false}, {"text": "니무 = Tree", "valid": false}, {"text": "누무 = Tree", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"I like cakes.\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "케이크를 좋아해요.", "valid": true}, {"text": "케이크가 맛없어요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "케이크를 좋아요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "케이크가 밋있어요.", "valid": false}]}], "1": [{"question": "Choose the correct answer.", "answers": [{"text": "가족 = family", "valid": true}, {"text": "작년 = this year", "valid": false}, {"text": "결혼하다 = to divorce", "valid": false}, {"text": "싫어하다 = to love", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"How long does it take from here?\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "여기에서 얼마나 걸려요?", "valid": true}, {"text": "저기에서 얼마나 걸려요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "여기에서 어떻게 걸려요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "얼마나 걸려요?", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"Where do I get off?\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "어디에서 내려요?", "valid": true}, {"text": "여기서 만나요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "지금 가요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "어디에서 볼까요?", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"I'm sorry that I'm late.\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "늦게와서 죄송해요.", "valid": true}, {"text": "일찍와서 죄송해요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "방금와서 감사해요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "늦게와서 고마워요.", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "Choose the correct answer.", "answers": [{"text": "우체국 = post office", "valid": true}, {"text": "숟가락 = chopsticks", "valid": false}, {"text": "젓가락 = spoons", "valid": false}, {"text": "공항 = airplane", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"Can you play tennis?\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "테니스 칠 수 있어요?", "valid": true}, {"text": "농구를 할 수 있어요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "축구를 좋아해요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "테니스 칠 수 없어요?", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"What movie do you want to see?\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "무슨 영화를 보고 싶어요?", "valid": true}, {"text": "어떤 드라마를 보고 싶어요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "어디 영화를 알고 싶어요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "무슨 영화를 볼 거예요?", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"010-5437-8126.\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "공일공 오사삼칠 팔일이육.", "valid": true}, {"text": "공일공 오삼칠사 팔이이육.", "valid": false}, {"text": "공일공 오삼삼사 팔일이육.", "valid": false}, {"text": "공일공 오사삼칠 팔이삼팔.", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"Why don't you work out?\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "운동하는 게 어때요?", "valid": true}, {"text": "공부하는 게 어때요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "노래하는 게 어때요?", "valid": false}, {"text": "걷는 게 어때요?", "valid": false}]}, {"question": "How do you say \"Jake is wearing sneakers.\" in Korean?", "answers": [{"text": "제이크는 운동화를 신고 있어요.", "valid": true}, {"text": "제이크는 운동화를 입고 있어요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "제이크는 운동화를 벗고 있어요.", "valid": false}, {"text": "제이크는 운동화를 사고 있어요.", "valid": false}]}]}

export default questions;
